<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Vecna]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/</link><image><url>https://flame-of-faerun.com/lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Vecna</title><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/</link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 21:24:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://flame-of-faerun.com/lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 21:24:34 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[11. December 17th, 2024 Baulder's Gate]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Waking up in somewhat of a panic, The Flame of Faerun scrambled to their feet and readied their weapons as the Dire Troll and the Wyvern bared down on them and a fight ensued. It was somewhat fortuitous that the Dire Troll and Wyvern had weakened each other. After the fight, Finn, the alchemist's apprentice, harvested the blood of the Dire Troll and Wyvern venom to be used for some potions and other alchemical creations later on.<br>On the road to Daggerford, where Finn was heading, and on the way to Waterdeep and eventually Neverwinter, the party stumbled across a group of lizardmen off the side of the road that seemed to be searching for something. Naively, they approached and the lizardmen attacked. They were dispatched of somewhat easily and the party looked for what the lizardmen were looking for. Eventually. <a class="internal-link" data-href="Flame Of Faerun/Leucius Alistar Stonewall.md" href="https://flame-of-faerun.com/flame-of-faerun/leucius-alistar-stonewall.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Leucius</a> found a red dragon egg buried under some mud. After much deliberation, the party took it with them and headed out.<br>Upon reaching Daggerford, more of a military outpost than a proper town. The party delivered Finn safely to his alchemist master who rewarded the party with some healing potions and a few vials of wyvern venom poison. The wyvern venom was now diluted enough that it wouldn't hurt you if it got on your skin, only if it got into your bloodstream.<br>That night, while resting, <a class="internal-link" data-href="Flame Of Faerun/Ingrid Evergleam.md" href="https://flame-of-faerun.com/flame-of-faerun/ingrid-evergleam.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Ingrid</a> had a vivid dream where they were turned into a mind flayer by their mother and woke up in the middle of the night in a cold sweat. Looking out their window, Ingrid saw a small child out in the middle of town...looking directly at their window. Upon going outside out of concern for the child. The child ran at Ingrid and turned into what to them, looked like Vecna before diving through them and disappearing. The rest of the party whom Ingrid had awoken did not see this. Ingrid passed out either out of fear, being passed through by a ghost or something. The rest of the party went back inside dragging Ingrid along with them, and Leucius made sure that they made it through the night safely.]]></description><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/session-notes/11.-december-17th,-2024-baulder's-gate.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/11. December 17th, 2024 Baulder's Gate.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 21:23:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Session Notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/session-notes/session-notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/Session Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 20:43:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>