<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Vecna]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/</link><image><url>https://flame-of-faerun.com/lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Vecna</title><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/</link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:48:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://flame-of-faerun.com/lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:48:06 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[9. October 22nd, 2024 Candlekeep]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The Flame of Faerun entered Candlekeep through the door from <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Alustriel Silverhand.md" href="https://flame-of-faerun.com/npcs/alustriel-silverhand.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Alustriel</a>'s Sanctuary in Sigil and were transported out the door of the smithy in Candlekeep's lower city. Candlekeep, while not as sizable as a city like Neverwinter or Baulder's Gate in geographical size, is still just as sizable in population. The lower city is packed full of shops and goods to buy, sell, and trade. The upper city contains those who are more wealthy, and the Great Library in the densely packed edge of the city on the coast.<br>Working towards the upper city, The Flame met a halfling in fairly nice clothing looking over a ledger. He was quite dismissive of the party until they asked for Sarah Siotta. He took them to the library that Sarah was at and told them to not touch anything. Once out of sight...they immediately started looking at and reading some of the books.<br>Sarah came out after a few minutes and asked them what they were looking for. Upon hearing about the book that mentions teleportation via an obelisk, Sarah went to retrieve the book but brought the party to where the book was where it was discovered that it was stolen with a large circular burned part of the wall that is large enough for someone to step through, if there was something to step through. Upon touching the burned mark, <a class="internal-link" data-href="Flame of Faerun/Leucius Alistar Stonewall.md" href="https://flame-of-faerun.com/flame-of-faerun/leucius-alistar-stonewall.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Leucius</a> got a vision of the library they found in the hideout of The Cult of Vecna back in Neverwinter.<br>After buying some equipment and getting a few upgraded items, The Flame of Faerun set out on the road to Neverwinter. Not too far off, they ran into an injured Adult White Dragon who was fairly hostile at first, but after <a class="internal-link" data-href="Flame of Faerun/Karma Armstrong.md" href="https://flame-of-faerun.com/flame-of-faerun/karma-armstrong.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Karma</a> gave a bit of healing to the dragon, it rewarded them with an amount of gold and then told them to leave...which they promptly did so. It was fairly odd to encounter a dragon, especially a white dragon considering the fairly temperate and high moisture climate they were traveling through. Later on, they noticed some spiderwebs across trees in the woods and encountered an injured elven woman who was in distress about her traveling companion who was taken by giant spiders, possibly back to their nest.<br>A bit down the road, the party was ambushed by a small contingent of giant spiders, and the injured elven woman proved to be an imposter and a giant spider herself. With a bit of convincing from <a class="internal-link" data-href="Flame of Faerun/SIldar Hallwinter.md" href="https://flame-of-faerun.com/flame-of-faerun/sildar-hallwinter.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">SIldar</a>, the party went to discover the nest and took out about 10 giant spiders, a few wolf spiders, and the queen who ended up falling down an abyss. Clearing out the eggs along the way, the party decided to use the former nest as a shelter to rest for the night, to continue the long road traveling to Neverwinter the next day.<br><img alt="Candlekeep-map.png" src="https://flame-of-faerun.com/lib/media/candlekeep-map.png">]]></description><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/session-notes/9.-october-22nd,-2024-candlekeep.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/9. October 22nd, 2024 Candlekeep.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:45:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://flame-of-faerun.com/lib/media/candlekeep-map.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="https://flame-of-faerun.com/lib/media/candlekeep-map.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Session Notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/session-notes/session-notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/Session Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:47:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>