<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Vecna]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/</link><image><url>https://flame-of-faerun.com/lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Vecna</title><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/</link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 03:00:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://flame-of-faerun.com/lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 03:00:52 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[Karma Armstrong]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>]]></description><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/flame-of-faerun/karma-armstrong.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Flame of Faerun/Karma Armstrong.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 01:58:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Leucius Alistar Stonewall]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>]]></description><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/flame-of-faerun/leucius-alistar-stonewall.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Flame of Faerun/Leucius Alistar Stonewall.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 01:58:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Oriana]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>]]></description><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/flame-of-faerun/oriana.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Flame of Faerun/Oriana.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 01:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Selene Foster]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>]]></description><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/flame-of-faerun/selene-foster.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Flame of Faerun/Selene Foster.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 01:59:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sildar Hallwinter]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>]]></description><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/flame-of-faerun/sildar-hallwinter.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Flame of Faerun/Sildar Hallwinter.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 01:59:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Flame of Faerun]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/flame-of-faerun/the-flame-of-faerun.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Flame of Faerun/The Flame of Faerun.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 02:02:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Alustriel Silverhand]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Alustriel Silverhand.jpg" src="https://flame-of-faerun.com/npcs/npc-pictures/alustriel-silverhand.jpg">Lady Alustriel Silverhand, called the Shining Lady, has been an influential wizard and proponent of good across Toril for centuries. Alustriel is one of the Seven Sisters—immortal daughters of Mystra, a god of magic. The divine energy Mystra passed to Alustriel grants Alustriel incredible power over arcane magic.<br>Alustriel’s youthful appearance as a human woman with silver hair gives no hint of her supernaturally extended life span. She typically wears long robes and wields a unicorn-headed staff, her&nbsp;Staff of Silverymoon.<br><br>Alustriel’s primary concerns are to spread kindness, reward virtue, and promote a culture of compassion throughout the multiverse. She is good at building alliances and quick to intervene when she senses a threat to the forces of good. She has traveled far and established safe houses across the planes—such as her sanctum in the city of Sigil. Alustriel doesn’t seek personal glory or wealth; her style of influencing the cosmos is quiet yet steady.<br><br>Like other Chosen of Mystra, Alustriel is concerned with preserving the Weave, the primary incarnation of magic that permeates Toril. She believes that the Weave favors those who act with mercy and compassion, seeks to deliver lives of security for all, and bolsters people’s efforts when they seek to right wrongs and combat evil.<br>Nowhere are Alustriel and her deeds better known than in the Silver Marches and its capital, Silverymoon. Alustriel ruled Silverymoon for centuries, once disguised as a wizard named Elué Dualen and then later in her true form. She helped create Silverymoon’s famous Moonbridge and cofounded the Lady’s College, the first school in Faerûn for mages as students rather than as apprentices in service.<br>Alustriel stepped down as Silverymoon’s high mage more than a century ago. Her son, Methrammar Aerasumé, now leads the city and works to uphold his mother’s legacy.<br>Alustriel has partaken in countless adventures before and after her tenure as Silverymoon’s high mage. She has befriended famous adventurers such as Drizzt Do’Urden, worked with prominent organizations like the Harpers, and helped prevent or undo many kinds of evil.]]></description><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/npcs/alustriel-silverhand.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPCs/Alustriel Silverhand.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 01:50:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://flame-of-faerun.com/npcs/npc-pictures/alustriel-silverhand.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="https://flame-of-faerun.com/npcs/npc-pictures/alustriel-silverhand.jpg"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Important NPCs]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><a class="internal-link" data-href="Alustriel Silverhand.md" href="https://flame-of-faerun.com/npcs/alustriel-silverhand.html" target="_self" rel="noopener">Alustriel Silverhand</a>]]></description><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/npcs/important-npcs.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPCs/Important NPCs.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 01:50:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[6. August 20th, 2024 The Obelisk's Secrets]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The Flame of Faerun continued clearing out Thundertree Ruins and eventually fought a Bone Roc in the main tower of the Thundertree ruins. Upon it's defeat, The Flame of Faerun found a fairly sizable chunk of black rock along with some treasure from the chest in the room.<br>Upon touching the stone, The Flame of Faerun felt themselves being pulled by almost a supernatural force. They found themselves transported to some otherworldly place where a woman with sunkissed skin and white hair was sitting reading a book, looked up, shocked by the party materializing in her home, and instinctively grabbed the wand at her side exlaiming "By the gods! Who are you, and how did you get into my home?!" After calming her concerns and introducing themselves, the woman introduced herself as <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Alustriel Silverhand.md" href="https://flame-of-faerun.com/npcs/alustriel-silverhand.html" target="_self" rel="noopener">Alustriel Silverhand</a> and told them about the Obelisk she had recently came into possession of, her accounts of her involvement with Vecna, and how they should procees with the recent developments with Vecna possibly resurfacing.<br>Alustriel concluded that the Obelisk could probably transport The Flame of Faerun close to the nearest shard if she concentrated hard enough. After telling the party that she believed the a shard was located in the mouth of a giant bronze statue of a frog. She told them that it was in a place called Thither, once home to a hag named Balvorna, but it may have moved since then. Alustriel then had the party touch the obelisk and she concentrated and teleported them close to the shard's location.<br>The Flame of Faerun found themselves moving through space, images warped in nightmarish blacks, dark and inky. A distant spot of color began to form, almost fog-like, but deep crimson. Red-washed scenery of a town with endless streets and alleyways stretch out, the buildings mostly in ruins. In the sky, engulfing the entire field of view is Vecna himself. The Flame recognized his raspy voice from when he materialized in the sewers. He spoke "I see you are growing closer, and that you travel within my realm. You may pass through for now. But there will be a time soon where we will meet and you will be my final key." The Flame of Faerun's vision went dark. As their eyes adjusted, they found themselves standing in front of a large majestic palace.]]></description><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/session-notes/6.-august-20th,-2024-the-obelisk's-secrets.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/6. August 20th, 2024 The Obelisk's Secrets.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 02:13:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[7. September 3rd, 2024 The Palace of Heart's Desire]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The Flame of Faerun started exploring the Palace and actually met a talking bear of all things along with some other people who were told to wait outside before they could get an audiance with Zybilna, the owner of the palace and this domain of the Feywild. Upon inspecting the garden they were in, they noticed a plaque with an inscription that read:<br>"The lion or the hart must wear the crown. But which one should it weigh down?"<br>Searching the garden for an answer, the party eventually made their way to a tower where an iron lion named 'Envy' stood guard and offered the following information:<br>
<br>“We and our counterpart were created as a pair to protect the gardens from intruders in Zybilna’s absence.”
<br>“Our presence here means that our mistress is gone. Where? We do not know.”
<br>“The palace receives visitors even in Zybilna’s absence. Guests are to remain in the garden pavilion until Zybilna deigns to grant them an audience. It is not our responsibility to protect visitors.”
<br>Asking information about the crown, Envy offered the following information:<br>
<br>“Zybilna created the crown as a key that guests can use to reach certain areas of the palace in her absence. The crown has two forms: one made of silver needles, the other of golden roses.”
<br>“To transform the crown of needles into its gold form, it must be placed on the brow of the correct iron guardian. Which of us, Envy or Wrath, is the correct guardian? We cannot say. Placing the crown on the incorrect guardian banishes the guardian to its demiplane, along with the crown.”
<br>“Once the crown is transformed into its gold form, either guardian can wear it without being banished. Certain doors inside the palace become unlocked or locked, depending on which guardian wears the golden crown.”
<br>The party eventually made their way to the pond in the garden after exploring the unlocked parts of the palace for a bit and a delicate hand made of water, black as winter’s night, silently broke the water’s surface. The hand clutched a crown made of silver needles. Below the hand, under the surface, a school of shimmering black fish takes on a vaguely humanoid form.<br>Once they took the crown, the holder heard the following riddle:<br>"The beginning of Whenever<br>
The end of Ever After<br>
The start of an age<br>
the finale of every moment<br>
the first in History"<br>This riddle was figured out to be fairly literal in it's meaning. The beginning of Whenever, 'W'; the end of Ever After, 'R'. Following this pattern the party figured the correct guardian to give the crown to was Wrath, the one they'd yet to meet. Leucius figured this out without the riddle, smart man.<br>Placing the crown on Wrath's head, the crown transformed into a crown of gold roses and the sound of a door unlocking was heard throughout the castle. All the doors with the hart above their doorframe could now be opened.<br>The party continued to explore the palace and eventually found Zybilna's butler, Thinnings. He revealed that everyone here was stuck in temporal stasis, save for the League of Manevolence, a group looking to steal a unicorn horn. Thinnings revealed that the unicorn horn can be used to break someone out of temporal stasis by touching the unicorn horn to them and speaking their true name. He knows that Zybilna is not Zybilna's true name and think's it is Iggwilv. Thinnings is unsure if there is a unicorn horn in the palace but encouraged searching the palace just in case there is one around.<br>The party eventually went downstairs from the top floor in the middle of the part of the castle surrounded by an ongoing thunderstorm, only to be met with Kelek and Warduke of the League of Malevolence. They were accompanied by two cockatrices and two Glasswork Golems whom Kelek summoned by speaking the rhyme "Knights of glass, protect my ass!". A battle ensued.]]></description><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/session-notes/7.-september-3rd,-2024-the-palace-of-heart's-desire.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/7. September 3rd, 2024 The Palace of Heart's Desire.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 03:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Session Notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/session-notes/session-notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/Session Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 01:51:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vecna Eve of Ruin - Home]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>For many years, the lich Vecna has imagined remaking existence. When this adventure starts, Vecna is already a god. Never truly satisfied, he yearns to become the most powerful being in the multiverse. Unfortunately for his enemies, Vecna recently devised the Ritual of Remaking to turn his dreams into reality.<br><br>Vecna’s Ritual of Remaking involves gathering powerful secrets, extracting energy from them, and interweaving this energy with the lich’s essence and magic. After Vecna and his cultists extract enough secrets, the lich plans to weave the ritual alone in the Cave of Shattered Reflection on the plane of Pandemonium.<br>The cave holds the power to harness energy and reveal fundamental truths, making it the perfect location for the ritual. The combined power of Vecna’s magic and the collected secrets reaches critical mass at the end of the ritual, triggering an explosion of sufficient magnitude to destroy Pandemonium and unravel the multiverse. Vecna, with his consciousness preserved inside a magical singularity, can then reknit the multiverse exactly as he wants, sealing the multiverse’s terrible fate.<br>Vecna plans to elevate himself above all others and to rewrite the histories and details of the entire multiverse. In Vecna’s new reality, all people serve him, he has never known defeat, and all who oppose him live in torment.<br>By the time this adventure begins, the lich has gathered a hoard of secrets and is nearly ready to begin the Ritual of Remaking. Only the characters can stop Vecna’s evil plan.<br><br><a data-href="Session Notes" href="https://flame-of-faerun.com/session-notes/session-notes.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Session Notes</a><br>
<a data-href="Important NPCs" href="https://flame-of-faerun.com/npcs/important-npcs.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Important NPCs</a><br>
<a data-href="The Flame of Faerun" href="https://flame-of-faerun.com/flame-of-faerun/the-flame-of-faerun.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Flame of Faerun</a>]]></description><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/vecna-eve-of-ruin-home.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Vecna Eve of Ruin - Home.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 02:03:07 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>