<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Vecna]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/</link><image><url>https://flame-of-faerun.com/lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Vecna</title><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/</link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 00:06:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://flame-of-faerun.com/lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 00:06:37 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[11. December 3rd, 2024 Baulder's Gate]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>After resting at the Dire Wolves' den, The Flame continued on their journey towards Baulder's Gate. They very quickly encountered an area that seemed to be stalked by something much larger, and much deadlier than anything they'd encountered so far. Carefully moving forward, they encountered an Owlbear who wasn't necessarily hostile, but also wasn't friendly at first. Being that they couldn't verbally communicate, they eventually followed the Owlbear's movements to find another, injured Owlbear. Providing help to the injured Owlbear, the two left without any further conflict. A good deed done for the day.<br>After arriving in Baulder's Gate, the party split up to gather some gear and do some trading. Trading some gems at a jewler's shop they got a good amount of gold, and Kavyl got himself a new suit at a tailor's shop. Down at the stables, they purchased a couple draft horses, a traveling wagon with built-in storage, a sleeping platform and a collapsible canopy. They also got all the bells and whistles with two sets of extra wheels, a rainproof cover, lanterns and brackets for traveling at night, and a chest mount which replaced a small part of the built-in storage where all their accessories were stored. It did take one day to have everything arranged but after making the payment and waiting, they were once again, on the road.<br>Along the way they encountered a particularly odd statue just off the road. It looked like a young man who was positioned as if he was running from something. Investigating further, the party decided to take the statue with them. After a full night with the statue in their possession, the statue actually turned out to be a man! The man, Finniard "Finn" Emberwick explained that he is an alchemist's assistant and got turned to stone by a cockatrice while he was on an assignment to collect some cockatrice feathers. (The Flame didn't mention that they debated selling the statue for some gold. Truly terrible people...)<br>That night, Ruga had a particularly interesting dream. She was in a mansion. It had pillars that seemed to reach the heavens, and stairs that seemed to stretch on for far too long and had an almost insurmountable height. She heard and felt the footsteps of a large being, along with the flapping of a cloak. The being was almost all bone, but had a particularly eerie and sinister aura about them. As the towering figure came into view, one hand was missing and replaced by an ethereal one, as was one of the eyes. Vecna came to haunt Ruga in her sleep. As a smile crept across Vecna's face, he reached down to grab Ruga, at which point she jolted awake to be met with not Vecna, but a Dire Troll running straight at her, with a Wyvern chasing close behind.]]></description><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/session-notes/11.-december-3rd,-2024-baulder's-gate.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/11. December 3rd, 2024 Baulder's Gate.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 00:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Session Notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/session-notes/session-notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/Session Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 00:05:55 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>