<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Vecna]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/</link><image><url>https://flame-of-faerun.com/lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Vecna</title><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/</link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:02:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://flame-of-faerun.com/lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:02:27 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[Ingrid Evergleam]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>]]></description><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/flame-of-faerun/ingrid-evergleam.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Flame of Faerun/Ingrid Evergleam.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 06:45:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kavyl Silkweaver the Highborn]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>]]></description><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/flame-of-faerun/kavyl-silkweaver-the-highborn.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Flame of Faerun/Kavyl Silkweaver the Highborn.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 06:46:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Flame of Faerun]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/flame-of-faerun/the-flame-of-faerun.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Flame of Faerun/The Flame of Faerun.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 06:44:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[10. November 19th, 2024 New Friends]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The Flame of Faerun rested in the now empty and cleared out Giant Spider cave and made way towards Neverwinter, planning to first stop at The Way Inn before arriving in Baulder's Gate.<br>On the way there, they ran across a wrecked caravan. Apparently they had been attacked and caught off guard as the guards they found were dead, having bled out on the side of the road. The toppled caravan, while offering nothing of material value, did house a scared and somewhat battered Deep Gnome who was actually on their way to Baulder's Gate. Since they were going the same way, they joined forces and The Flame of Faerun gained a new ally and party member in <a data-href="Kavyl Silkweaver the Highborn" href="https://flame-of-faerun.com/flame-of-faerun/kavyl-silkweaver-the-highborn.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Kavyl Silkweaver the Highborn</a>.<br>After arriving at The Way Inn, the party met a fairly friendly cat, and an interesting character by the name of <a data-href="Ruga" href="https://flame-of-faerun.com/flame-of-faerun/ruga.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Ruga</a>. Ruga had heard that the party had some sort of connection to Vecna and due to their own reasons, sought them out to figure out what they knew and if they would be allies or foes. It was also revealed, after spilling a whole mug of 'real' dwarven ale all over <a class="internal-link" data-href="Flame of Faerun/Leucius Alistar Stonewall.md" href="https://flame-of-faerun.com/flame-of-faerun/leucius-alistar-stonewall.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Leucius</a> that the cat they had met was actually an owlin druid known as <a data-href="Ingrid Evergleam" href="https://flame-of-faerun.com/flame-of-faerun/ingrid-evergleam.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Ingrid Evergleam</a>. After some conversation, it was determined that Ruga, Ingrid, and The Flame of Faerun were allies and were to join forces in figuring out exactly what was happening with Vecna and his followers.<br>Through the night, they drank the 'real' dwarven ale that they were told was brewed directly on sight by their server, Jasmine. While unsure of this claim, it was clear that it was in fact very potent as both Ingrid and Leucius didn't even finish a mug before being heavily intoxicated. Sildar made a passing comment that they couldn't 'hold their alcohol'. Sildar has also been around the block and is a bit too old for this shit and probably is used to drinking heavily as some sort of coping mechanism. Along the way, Ingrid was kicked out for destroying a painting, and a wall, with a drunken Guiding Bolt. It was later revealed, that this painting was a portrait of the widely reveared Baulduran, a legendary seafaring trader and explorer whom Baulder's Gate takes it's namesake from. This caused Ingrid to almost have an existential crisis, but they got through it with some convincing and 'strong suggestions'.<br>Back on the Trade Way, the party was ambushed by a pack of Dire Wolves. While a bit rough, they managed to defeat the wolves and took shelter in a nearby cave which seemed to have been the dire wolves' den, resting up before heading back out.]]></description><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/session-notes/10.-november-19th,-2024-new-friends.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/10. November 19th, 2024 New Friends.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:02:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Session Notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>https://flame-of-faerun.com/session-notes/session-notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/Session Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 19:46:34 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>