<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Vecna]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Vecna</title><link></link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 22:34:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 22:34:30 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator></dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[1. June 18th, 2024 Meet me in Phandalin]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Oriana, the Eladrin Druid from the Neverwinter Wood is strapped to a chair, she is held by leather straps when Reidoth, her mentor, tells her everything will be ok and to not worry. After being injected with something, the leather snaps, bones snap, and suddenly Oriana stands up seeing Reidoth being afraid of her for the first time, and in the reflection of a tray that has fallen to the ground, Oriana can see the deep black eyes with sickly green-yellow iris' looking back at her, tendrils where her mouth would be, as she has undergone Ceremorphosis, becoming a Mind Flayer.<br>Suddenly Oriana is awoken on the wagon the party took to Phandalin that the got from Gundren Rockseeker to deliver some goods for him and Myron, Selene's good friend and owner of the Sweet Dreams Casino in Neverwinter. She remembers the rest of her rag-tag group of companions:<br>Karma Armstrong - A young human cleric searching for his long lost adventuring parents<br>
Dior - A saytr paladin who is only along due to the promise of grand adventure<br>
Leucius Alistar Stonewall - A somewhat disgraced Noble of Neverwinter who is looking to free himself of his patron.<br>
Selene Foster - a human rogue who has made a life of thievery by necessity and also 'works' at a casino.<br>Coming up on the site of some scuffle with 2 horses, the party discovers Gundren Rockseeker and his accompaniment, Sildar Hallwinter have been attacked. Subsequently, the party is ambushed.<br>After defeating the goblins and going to take down their hideout, the party finds a rock on the floor that is warm to the touch. A symbol is cut out, a hand holding an eye. Karma, the human cleric determines that this is the Symbol of Vecna...a disturbing discovery.<br>After Freeing Sildar, with much thanks to the party, specifically Leucius and Selene, the party departed for Phandalin. ]]></description><link>session-notes/1.-june-18th,-2024-meet-me-in-phandalin.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/1. June 18th, 2024 Meet me in Phandalin.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 21:30:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2. July 2nd, 2024 Welcome to Phandalin]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The party arrived in Phandalin without trouble after taking down the Goblin Hideout and got themselves acquainted with the town. They got rooms, food, and some equipment before turning in for the night as it had gotten pretty late and they were exausted.<br>During the night, Sildar awoke to an odd fog rolling from west to east. This also awoke and intrigued the rest of the party and they headed over to investigate near Tresendar Manor. <br>As they approach, the air changed to a chill, almost hostile to the lungs themselves as the gates to the manor hang open and it looks fairly run down for a Mayoral Estate. Little did they know, they'd stumbled into a house of death.<br>Investigating the manor, they ran into little trouble, mainly looting what they did find and taking out an animated armor and spector that did attack them. They also meet the ghost of Thornboldt and Rosavalda Durst, the children of the Durst family whom owns the manor.<br>After the party does a bit more looting, they enter a basement area that is pretty musty. It seems as if it's been abandoned for some time.]]></description><link>session-notes/2.-july-2nd,-2024-welcome-to-phandalin.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/2. July 2nd, 2024 Welcome to Phandalin.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 21:40:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[3. July 16th, 2024 Death House]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>After entering the Basement, the party quickly discovers it is some sort of crypt. They are attacked by a number of creatures as they explore and gain some items, A grick from an alcove in the dining area, some ghouls in a hallway, and a mimic disguised as a door.<br>After resting, they find some ghasts in a bedroom which they quickly defeat, and gain some useful equipment from the chest at the foot of the bed. <br>Going deeper into the basement, they hear chanting, an eerie sign of what lies ahead. They discover a prison area where they find cloaks with the symbol of Vecna. This suggests that the Durst family were followers of Vecna and hosted some of the cult in this underground area. As they enter an alter room, they are drawn to the alter where cultists appear around them, the Symbol of Vecna tatooed on the backs of their hands and call for a sacrafice.<br>Refusing, the cult releases an undead shambling mound on the party. Unfortunately, Dior is engulfed and unable to be saved, perishing during the fight. After being defeated, the whole structure tries to kill the party as if it has a mind of it's own. Luckily the party escapes and the mists that first drew them to the Death House deposit them near the gates of Neverwinter.]]></description><link>session-notes/3.-july-16th,-2024-death-house.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/3. July 16th, 2024 Death House.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 21:46:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[4. July 30th, 2024 The Flame is Born]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Making it back to Neverwinter, the party is stopped outside of Neverwinter, where they adopt the name The Flame of Faerun as their name, but are not on the manifest of who is allowed in and out of Neverwinter. The guard gives them a break and allows them inside as long as they go straight to the adventuring guild and register themselves so that they are on the manifest going forward.<br>The party follows his instructions and they meet with a spunky halfling who heckles them a bit before calling one of her employees, Dianna to register them and give them their rank necklaces. She explains the ranks as follows:<br>Bronze - Given Necklaces with a copper bar that are given to new adventurers and allow them to take quests from the bulletin board of appropriate level. They also are required to be on patrol once per week.<br>
Silver - Necklaces are replaced with a silver bar and are able to take on more dangerous, but also more rewarding quests, required to patrol once every two weeks.<br>
Gold - Necklaces now have a gold bar an even more dangerous and rewarding quests are available. Patrol is required once per month<br>
Platinum - Very seasoned adventurers. There are four indentations in this new bar. Patrol required once every months.<br>
Platinum II - The second level of Platinum. One indentation is filled with a small gem.<br>
Paltinum III - The third level of Platinum rank adventurers, two indentations are now filled. This is currently the highest rank achieved by anyone in the guild. Patrol required once every six months.<br>
Platinum VI - The fourth level of Platinum rank. Three indentations are filled. Patrol required once per year, for 7 consecutive days.<br>
Platinum V - The highest rank available, only given to those who have achieved great feats of heroism. Four indentations are filled. They are given a ceremony and feast by Lord Nevermember.<br>The patrol is required due to an agreement between Lord Nevermember and the Guild. The guild is allowed to be in Neverwinter as long as they provide policing and peacekeeping measures in Neverwinter.<br>The Flame of Faerun (hereby referred to as The Flame) starts their first patrol after getting accommodations, some provided by the guild. Nothing lavish, a basic room no bigger than a large prison cell.  The Flame hears an aguished scream from an alley where they meet Kevori Fearnehart and her brother Delvin Fearnehart. Kevori is holding Delvin in her arms as he appears to have been murdered after being outed as an undercover agent investigating the Cult of Vecna in Neverwinter. He drops a desiccated eye that he used to access the cult's hideout.<br>The Flame takes the eye and uses it to be guided to the Cult's hideout. Here, in the catacombs, they come across a ghost whole has lost their identity and they help her remember herself as Chanelle Hallwinter, no relation to Sildar, who has stayed with the party even after stating many times that he is "Too old for this shit".<br>Exploring the catacombs, The Flame discovers that the Cult of Vecna is definately operating here and find the leader of their sect to be conducting some sort of ritual.]]></description><link>session-notes/4.-july-30th,-2024-the-flame-is-born.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/4. July 30th, 2024 The Flame is Born.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 22:04:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[5. August 13th, 2024 A Friend in Need]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The Flame confronted the cult leader, Zalryr, who had pulled Shadows out of two, seemingly willing, cult members. They defeated the cult and were greeted by a visage of Vecna who told them "Good news, Zalryr. Though your efforts have been disappointing, you have brought me new... points of interest...Yes, there is great potential here. May we meet again—but until then, I have my eye on you."<br>The Flame also felt them gain some sort of power and were given charms from Vecna, creating a link between them, and the God of Secrets.<br>Coming back from the catacombs and reporting to Lord Nevermember, they were given 100gp each and another 10gp for bringing a member of the cult back alive. They were given a piece of paper as proof of completion and after reporting to the guild, they had achieved Silver Rank in record time. Taking a quest off the bulletin board, it appeared Oriana's mentor, Reidoth was in trouble at the Ruins of Thundertree, being overrun with plant monsters, undead, giant spiders, cult members, and some large bird made of bones. The Flame headed out and cleared out a small portion of the ruins before finding Reidoth. They continued to clear out the ruins, marking places as safe as they did so, and decided to rest in a safe space before clearing out the rest of the ruins. ]]></description><link>session-notes/5.-august-13th,-2024-a-friend-in-need.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/5. August 13th, 2024 A Friend in Need.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 22:11:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Session Notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>session-notes/session-notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/Session Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 22:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vecna Eve of Ruin - Home]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>For many years, the lich Vecna has imagined remaking existence. When this adventure starts, Vecna is already a god. Never truly satisfied, he yearns to become the most powerful being in the multiverse. Unfortunately for his enemies, Vecna recently devised the Ritual of Remaking to turn his dreams into reality.<br><br>Vecna’s Ritual of Remaking involves gathering powerful secrets, extracting energy from them, and interweaving this energy with the lich’s essence and magic. After Vecna and his cultists extract enough secrets, the lich plans to weave the ritual alone in the Cave of Shattered Reflection on the plane of Pandemonium.<br>The cave holds the power to harness energy and reveal fundamental truths, making it the perfect location for the ritual. The combined power of Vecna’s magic and the collected secrets reaches critical mass at the end of the ritual, triggering an explosion of sufficient magnitude to destroy Pandemonium and unravel the multiverse. Vecna, with his consciousness preserved inside a magical singularity, can then reknit the multiverse exactly as he wants, sealing the multiverse’s terrible fate.<br>Vecna plans to elevate himself above all others and to rewrite the histories and details of the entire multiverse. In Vecna’s new reality, all people serve him, he has never known defeat, and all who oppose him live in torment.<br>By the time this adventure begins, the lich has gathered a hoard of secrets and is nearly ready to begin the Ritual of Remaking. Only the characters can stop Vecna’s evil plan.<br><br><a data-href="Session Notes" href="session-notes/session-notes.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Session Notes</a>]]></description><link>vecna-eve-of-ruin-home.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Vecna Eve of Ruin - Home.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 22:33:44 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>